Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Episode 91
Alaaddin.
Wake up, brother.
Alaaddin!
Come on, Alaaddin!
Wake up!
We need to get out of here.
This is so bad, brother.
We are a trump card in the hands of
the infidel.
We won't be for too long.
We will escape, brother.
Come on!
No soldiers are around.
My Allah, give me strength.
What is this?
Are you trying to escape?
Look, some fun for us.
The man who could bend this iron
would not have been captured.
Don't cause trouble, kid!
Neither iron nor walls can hold the Turk,
you infidel!
Open this lock so that I can show you.
Does a dog ever enter a wolf's den,
brother?
If it is to die, it does, brother.
You will see now!
I know what to do with you!
After Osman is killed, it will be your
turn anyway.
Allah!
Did you see my power now?
You dogs!
Let us go!
My Osman Bey won't let you get away
with this!
He will destroy your castle upon you when
he hears this!
Osman will die too! There is no hope
for you!
Shut up and at least don't die tired!
Come on! Enough resting!
We have to set off!
Our duty is hard!
Alps!
Keep your eyes open and be careful!
We are going to a wedding but our swords
will be sharp.
We are going to conquer!
Come on!
Come on, sisters! Come on!
People are coming!
I hope this ends up well.
Bala!
-Malhun!
-Bala!
They kidnapped the children!
What? Who? When?
There is no time. They took the kids
to Bilecik!
-Let's go to Bilecik then. Come on!
-Come on!
Osman Bey is coming!
Osman!
They kidnapped the children!
I know, Malhun.
I know.
What if something happens to our children,
Osman?
It won't.
They attacked Kosses as well.
But he went to the tribe now.
If they had wanted to try to kill our
children...
...they wouldn't take them to Bilecik.
What is their intention?
To use them against us?
They were going to kill us at the Castle.
They are doing this so that our children
don't seek revenge.
They have known us for so long.
Of course, they know we won't go
there unprepared.
That's why they want to hit us at
our weak spot.
But I will neither leave my children to
them...
...nor let them live!
All right, then! Let's destroy Bilecik
upon them!
No.
Malhun...
...we won't act out of pain.
We will act by our minds.
Osman is dead.
Osman will sit right here.
And the assassins will be here.
There will be also Justinyanus' soldiers
besides yours.
What difference does it make where
Osman sits?
I like a precaution.
You taught me not to belittle anyone
in war, Master.
I won't leave an open door.
You say the most right words, Nikola.
Aya Nikola, Master Arius...
...this is the Bilecik Castle.
But the history will remember this castle
as the graves of Turk beys.
I have no doubt.
Jugglers outside, actors, musicians...
...they all have a dagger on their belts.
They are thirsty for Turkish blood.
Did you tell them about their actual goal?
Of course, I didn't.
I didn't say so that the information
wouldn't leak.
They think is it only for precaution.
When the war gets closer, they will find
out Bilecik will be covered in blood.
But the Turks won't be full.
They are fasting.
Their sacred iftar will be their last
meal.
Congratulations, Justinyanus!
You are not a coward like your uncle
Rogatus.
The peace that has ruled this land for
years with the order of Emperor...
...ends tonight.
What about Osman's children?
What will happen to them?
No one will touch them.
They will wait for me.
You can kill the alps, the women and even
Osman with pleasure.
First, we will find out where our children
are.
We won't fall into those dogs' traps who
want to kill us.
Clearly, this is their move.
You are right, Osman Bey.
If we take precautions for the wedding...
...they will want us to attack out of
anger.
We will be cautious.
What is your order, my Bey?
We set off to take the Bilecik Castle.
They abducted our children.
They attacked Kosses.
They want to secure their work.
So will we!
But we don't have anything to threaten
them.
We are walking towards an ambush,
Osman Bey.
How will we manage?
You will see, Turgut Bey.
My children will be with me before the sun
goes down.
And Bilecik Castle will be our property.
I hope so.
I hope so, my Bey.
Justinyanus surprised us by telling us
what will happen in this hall...
...Master Arius.
Would you like to tell us what will happen
outside?
When there will be a massacre in
the Castle...
...when Osman's lineage ends Söğüt and
the tribe will be without a leader.
-And Barkın--
-How?
Isn't Barkın going to die?
Justinyanus...
...true loyalty is what everyone does not
know.
Barkın has been loyal to me for years.
Just like you have been.
But Kosses is not like that, is he?
Kosses is dead.
Done.
You, Justinyanus, will kill Osman and
the others.
Barkım will take Söğüt.
Söğüt got very wealthy.
Osman got very wealthy.
You will get your share as well.
Don't worry.
And I will take my mines.
What about you, Master Arius?
What will you do?
I'll destroy his catapults before I turn
his skull into a slurry.
I will destroy their weapons.
Osman is making preparations for a
conquest.
I will ruin his dream.
Someone will take over the sanjaks
that the Turks consider sacred.
Don't forget, Justinyanus.
You can't stop the Turks by killing them.
You must put a man who will serve
you at their head.
That man is Barkın.
The war has begun.
Only Osman doesn't know it.
Come on.
They set the trap in the Castle but
continue to attack on the road.
Who else is on the road?
The wedding convoy, my Bey.
Right.
Since they took our children as trumps...
...we won't go there empty-handed.
We will take Yarhisar Lord's daughter,
Holofira.
We will raid the wedding convoy.
Well.
Bala, Malhun...
...you will come to the castle with me
acting like you don't know about children.
If you consider this appropriate then I
will hold my anger back...
...and do as you order, Osman Bey.
We will wait for your sign.
Thank you.
Turgut Bey...
...you will make the raid with alps.
Send Holofira to the tribe.
You will come to the Bilecik Castle with
her stepfather Basilius.
We can't enter the castle any other way.
We will manage.
But the children...
...how will we save the children?
There is someone who can find them and
inform us.
Who is it, my Bey.
My nephew, Aktemur.
Walk freely in your castle for now.
You won't even be able to take a step
when it becomes the Turks' property.
Holofira.
I've raised you for these days.
You are left to me by your mother.
I married her for power.
Even though you are not my daughter...
...I accepted you.
You will do the same.
We only act for the sake of the sacred
Rome.
This marriage...
...will make us even stronger.
I don't want to be strong.
I want to be happy.
Lord Basileus!
Get out of your hole!
What does this mean, Turgut Bey?
After all these years of peace?
We will accompany you to Bilecik.
Let's see if the dagger against our throat
belongs to you.
Damn it!
Soldiers!
Alps!
You have nowhere to run, Lord!
Your head seems to be heavy for your body,
Lord!
Don't worry...
...we will relieve you of that burden.
Attack!
Be careful, Cerkutay!
We have not fought side by side for a
long time and that's what you say?
Did you miss it?
I missed the fight but...
...I didn't miss your talking while
fighting, Cerkutay!
Fine, then I will shut up and let my
swords talk!
Good for you!
Konuralp! The Lord is running away!
Come on, little girl.
Come on.
Don't worry, we won't hurt you.
Are you all like this?
You are like my Mari.
It was unclear what she would do as well.
Alps!
Boran!
Protect the girl.
I will take your father and return.
Don't worry. Our brothers would never
hurt you.
I say I will accompany you.
You are still trying to escape, Basilius.
Will you stop us alone?
You say so?
Who said he was alone?
Turgut Bey...
...you will pay for this.
We don't answer to snakes.
We only ask!
Attack!
You've ruined all these years of peace!
You liar!
You pretend to be innocent by standing
in front of me and saying peace!
Say it, the wedding we planned was
supposed to be your funeral!
Say it!
I know how to make you tell the truth!
In front of your daughter!
Come on!
Girl...
...why are you crying?
We didn't kidnap you.
We saved you.
Don't be afraid.
Wipe your tears.
The man who is your stepdad is
using you for his own purposes.
You are a stunning, brave girl.
Father!
Tell her.
Tell her!
When I gave Holofira...
...the Lord would make me a partner
in his trade.
He also gave a lot of property from
his castle.
Also...
...it was a great move to kill you!
This is your stepfather's true face.
I'm no different than the animals
you raise for your benefit!
The Turks you call our enemies treat me
better than you!
I hate you!
Aygül Hatun, you take Holofira to
the tribe.
Then inform her aunt at once.
Cerkutay...
...you catch up with Osman Bey.
Inform him about what happened.
Come on, brother.
This, Basileus is...
...coming to the wedding with us!
You are invited as well, you dog!
You too!
So you get the iron from here, Osman.
Let's see where you forge all this iron.
Did you load them all?
Nothing is left!
Good.
Be very careful.
Come on.
We will be the breath of death on
their necks! Come on!
My Bey, the mission is completed.
We have the Lord.
His daughter Holofira is going to
the tribe with alps, my Bey.
Then let's go to our future estate!
Come on!
Bilecik Castle
My soldiers!
Many enemies have stood at the gates
of Rome to this day.
Arabs, Mongols, and thousands of
barbarians.
But they were never this close.
We are the fire!
Whoever approaches us will perish!
We bid farewell to the Turks permanently
tonight.
We have Osman's sons.
He is coming to the wedding as well.
We will hit them on the iftar table.
We won't separate women, children or
old people.
Everyone in the courtyard and the castle
will die!
Who wants to shed Turkish blood?
We do! We do! We do! We do!
Death to the Turks!
-For Great Caesar!
-For Great Rome!
Sir, Osman and his people are coming.
My friend Osman Bey.
Let's welcome him.
Tell me, Selcen Hatun...
...who kidnapped my Shahzadas?
Baysungur Alp said their faces were
covered, my Sheik.
They look like those vile people
we knew years ago.
I hope this is good.
Bismillah.
Mother.
In the name of Allah!
Get out!
Open the way!
Selcen Mother, Osman Bey sent him.
Kosses is heavily wounded.
We must help.
To the healing tent, Valiants! Come on!
Come on!
You, come here!
Could my Osman find my grandchildren?
He will soon, mother.
Who did this?
Orhan and Alaaddin's kidnapper was
the Lord of Yarhisar.
The one who wounded Kosses is
his commander.
My children!
May my Allah protect our Shahzadas
from the cruelty of the enemy.
Amen.
-Hatuns.
-My Sheik.
I will check on Kosses.
You keep praying for our Shahzadas and
Kosses.
Of course, my Sheik.
Come on.
Come on, mother. Let's go.
My Allah, may you protect my children.
How is he, Kumral Abdal?
This is a terrible wound, my Sheik.
But there is always hope.
In the name of Allah!
Allah is the healer!
Send the rain of mercy on this servant
of yours.
Grant him the remedy.
For the sake of your prophet Muhammed
Mustafa...
...for the sake of holy Jesus...
...heals the wounds of this wounded
servant.
Grant him healing, my Rabb!
In the name of Allah!
Bilecik Castle
Wait, we have to search you for
precautions.
Search them!
You may pass.
Where they hide is close.
Their number is increasing.
We will find their den.
Come on!
Welcome Osman bey.
Thank you, Thank you.
I will have a special iftar table for you.
We'll have our wedding after the iftar.
You can rest in your rooms if you want.
Well thought, Justinianus.
The road was tiring.
You are right, Osman Bey.
We should rest a bit.
It's okay.
Follow me, Osman Bey.
Hey Masha Allah! (praise be!)
This new iron mine is great!
The weapon made of this iron
will be unbeaten!
Our intentions are clear.
So Allah makes it all easy for us.
Open your eyes widely.
There will be no one, even birds,
that doesn't stand with us!
Come on my valiants!
Unload it!
Chunk it up!
So you this is where they forge
and produce weapons.
Their dream is great.
But they'll grumble in the gizzard.
Command us to destoy them, my Bey!
Not now, Husamettin.
Not now.
We'll let them grow up.
The bigger they are...
...the noiser their destruction is.
First of all...
I'll talk to Beys.
I'll make sure they are loyal.
We are going back to the tribe.
Wait here.
Keep your eyes open just in case.
Yes!
Where are you headed?
To the Red Apple.
Son.
My valiant son.
I missed you a lot.
I missed you very much, father.
This is Osman Bey's order.
Alp Temur is on duty.
Ayse, does she know that?
I have not been to myself since Fatma
went to the tableland.
How did you manage to wait for years,
Gunduz Bey?
Being the state requires devotion.
Masha Allah (Praise be).
Masha Allah (Praise be) to my son.
We thought you were still a child.
You are already ready to fight, valiant.
Temur, tell us.
Where are the kids?
Do you know where they are?
They are locked in the dungeon.
It shows the dungeon's location.
I'll come again, but now I have to leave.
I'll let you know if I learn anything.
Thank you, Alp Temur.
May Allah help you.
Father.
Be careful.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be).
Like father like son.
Eyvallah (thank you) Malhun Hatun.
It's like he said.
We know where the dungeon is.
Now listen to me carefully.
We'll get rid of the chain, brother.
How are we going to do this?
Look at it, it's so tough.
We'll find a way.
If we can't break the chain,
we can grab the keys.
Osman Bey must be coming to
save us.
Say what you have to say, Alaeddin.
I think we should wait for him, brother.
I knew you'd say that.
You choose waiting when it's hard.
What can we do, brother?
What do you want me to do?
Let's give it a try, brother.
We'll break it if we can loose it,
Inshallah.
Okay brother.
One, two, tree...
Ya Haqq!
Check that out!
You'll burn!
You put a lot of effort.
And a lot of gold.
It's all worth it though, Osman Bey.
Here.
Herd of cowards!
It's been many years, they are still
not brave enough to face us!
They can't stand against us. They can only
threaten us with the lives of our children.
We are not going to let those cruels
have our kids, no matter what happens!
Don't worry, Hatuns. They are
the grandchildren of Ertugrul Ghazi.
They'll figure something out.
We entered the castle.
It's haram for us to leave without them!
May our fight be blessed!
- Let's go.
One is approaching.
- Gunduz Bey.
- Cerkutay!
We came to finish a cruel,
almost ended up finishing you.
The show shall begin.
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
His nickname is Ceaser.
He has never been beaten.
I am glad to have him on our side.
What if he was our enemy?
Masha Allah, (praise be)
He fights well.
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
However, we never say to anyone that
"what if he was our enemy?"
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
Alps.
Tell me.
Anyone want to confront Caesar?
I can go my Bey.
Gence Bey.
He can't even take a punch of mine.
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
I'll confront him, my Bey.
Samil!
Tell me.
Do you want to fight Caesar?
I have come all the way to fight.
Not one,
I'll fight one thousand Caesars my Bey!
Eyvallah.
- Turhan?
- My Bey?
My breast is hotter than
the Blacksmith's iron. I am ready my Bey.
But I want Abdurrahim to fight.
Sisters!
No one is around.
Be careful.
Ah, my belly!
I can't wait more!
Ah! Ah!
What are you doing here?
You should be in your rooms
until the supper.
We need a doctor!
A doctor! My belly hurts!
Ah! Ah!
What are you looking at?
Hatun is fighting for his life!
Is this how you host your guests?
We need a doctor!
Okay. Go to your room.
We'll get a doctor.
We have no time to wait!
We'll go by ourselves.
Go to your rooms now.
We'll get you a doctor.
What's happening?
They want a doctor, sir.
Go back to your duty.
I'll take care of it.
Hay Masha Allah, my valiant.
You came just in time!
The cellar is at the end of the corridor.
It's time for shift change.
There'll be two guards.
Be careful.
Son you be careful too, okay?
Let's go Hatuns.
Thank my Lord.
He opened his eyes.
Kossess?
How are you?
Are you better?
Sheik Edebali.
Thank you.
Osman.
I and Osman...
Kids, Orhan, Alaeddin.
Did Osman save them?
Eesy, Kosses, easy.
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
Move slowly.
Did he save the kids?
Osman is at Bilecik Castle now.
He'll get our shahzades back
in here safe and sound, Inshallah.
Sheik Edebali...
I know...
You don't have great reaction
to things.
But I am still surprised to see you
so calm...
...when your grandchildren are abducted.
How can I reject what comes from Allah,
Kosses?
It seems like evil, but there
may be wisdom and goodness hidden inside.
I entrusted my shahzades to Allah.
Osman Bey and their mothers
took precautions and went for them.
They'll come back with
Orhan and Alaeddin Inshallah.
Inshallah.
I could never stay calm like that.
Thank Allah, both our heart and our
beloved ones are entrusted to Allah.
What we need to do is to
pray with patience.
Sorry to trouble you.
You took care of me among
all those troubles.
Nothing is trouble about taking care
of the life that Allah has given, Kosses.
It wouldn't mean anything if we left
you with your wounds...
...and start grieving for our shahzades.
I am not from your religion.
But I am lucky to be your friend.
I appreciate it, Sheik Edebali.
Be a friend, or an enemy.
Be a Muslim, or not...
If you are hungry, oppressed or wounded
in the land of Muslims...
...that Muslim will find cure
as he heals you.
It doesn't matter if you share
the same religion or not.
Mercy is what's left us from
the messenger of Allah.
Peace be upon him.
The compasssionate Allah...
put the blue sky and brave ground
in the service of the whole humanity.
What we need to do is to show mercy
for whoever needs it.
Our fight against the cruel...
...and our opposition against the devil...
...comes from
our compassion for the innocents.
-Eyvallah.
Abdurrahim.
Go show what you got.
As you command, my Bey.
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
It's dangerous when the
armor is off, Osman Bey.
If you want to...
No.
Armor makes us heavy.
Continue.
Come on!
Caesar! Caesar! Caesar!
Boo! Boo!
Get up!
Caesar couldn't take care of Abdurrahim,
Justinianus.
Summon a couple more soldiers...
And make it fair.
It's okay for me.
Soldiers!
Show our friends how hospitable we are!
Hit! Hit! Hit!
No way, we'll fight too, Gence Bey.
- Lucky for us.
- Stop, valiants.
My Bey asked me.
Abdurrahim is enough.
Let's watch.
Hit! Hit! Hit!
Get up! Get up!
Kill him!
It was a fair fight.
Your men fought well.
But Abdurrahim cannot be beaten.
Thanks, Osman Bey.
My Bey!
Kids are in the dungeon.
Bala Hatun is around them.
We are waiting for your command.
We are waiting for iftar.
We are with you at iftar.
What did you cook for us?
I have unbelievable meals for you.
Is that so?
Eyvallah.
Bilecik Castle.
- I have no power left.
- Hang on.
You carry Ertugrul Ghazi's blood, brother!
Don't give up.
Come on, one more time.
One, two, three...
Ya Haqq!
They are moving, brother.
We have to do what we have to do now.
Come on brother, let's do it.
One, two, three...
Ya Haqq!
KIZILBEYOGLU TRIBE
Martados informed that Osman Bey is going
to be murdered tonight in Bilecik Castle.
Murdered?
We have to tell people and
unite, Barkin Bey.
We have to depart to Bilecik.
We can't leave Osman Bey alone.
Do you think that
I didn't think of it?
I sent my alps to Kayi tribe immediately.
They'll go to Bilecik from there.
I did what I needed to.
But anything can happen.
The ones who want to kill Osman Bey
won't leave Sogut alone.
Sogut is Turk's land!
We are not to leave there without a leader.
Therefore, I will manage Sogut.
Barkin Bey is not right.
This is disobeying Osman Bey.
I don't accept it.
I am okay with helping Sogut but...
claiming the authority is not acceptable.
Beys! Osman Bey is closer to me than
he is to any of you!
I prefer managing Sogut to
losing my land!
Headless herd is invaded by jackals!
Now tell me.
Are we going to let Turk's flag down
because Osman Bey is not around?
Someone has to raise that flag.
Barkin what are you doing?
You lied to Beys!
You didn't sent alps to the tribe.
There's no explanation of this!
Hatun.
I had to do it to protect
the legacy of your father and uncle.
I cannot let the infidels decide on
the fate of our community...
...just because of Osman Bey's conceit.
Bilecik Castle
I guess this is time for you to eat.
Eyvallah.
It's iftar time.
Thank Allah.
When are we going to act, sir?
We are waiting for all of them,
don't hurry.
Come on.
Damn it!
They run away!
Search the castle!
You!
Where are you going?
Bala Hatun.
Go to the cellar to get the weapons.
Go.
Let's go Hatuns.
What are you doing here?
We found what we were looking for.
Come on.
I'd love to cut them with my double sword.
I'll have to be satisfied with this one.
Let's go Cerkutay.
You!
We found it, thank Allah!
Come on.
Hatuns!
We have to break the fast,
even when there's a war.
Our mouth is free now.
Here you go.
Come on.
In the name of Allah.
Amen.
Let's go.
Sisters.
Open the door!
Hey insiders!
Open it!
Soldiers pop up everywhere!
They must have borrowed all the
soldiers from other Lords!
Cowards!
They can gather whoever they want.
We'll overcome with Osman Bey's plan.
Open the door!
Empower us my Allah!
Master Davut would know how to get rid
of this if he were here.
Brother, come on.
The chain is about to loose.
- We'll get out of here.
- We will, brother.
One, two, three...
Ya Haqq!
Sir, the wedding procession is about to
enter Bilecik.
Congratulations, Justinianus.
Congratulations.
Inegol Castle
My caravans has passed here for years.
I put my men on their tail
tens of times.
I followed them, but...
I couldn't find them.
It is really, really strange that
they built their headquarters there.
As he is going to die tonight,
he does not pose danger.
I'll ruin...
...their headquarters first.
Then I will burn all their catapults
that they made to demolish my walls.
And..
...my mine!
You lost your mine...
...but you'll regain it now.
Sir, we are ready to attack.
These lands will enlighten with
the fire we light.
What am I going to do now?
What will happen to me?
Don't cry, beautiful daughter.
Uh, don't cry.
Osman Bey saved you from those ignobles,
just like how you wanted.
Now he'll send you to your aunt.
Don't be afraid, my beautiful daughter.
You are decent people.
I appreciate you.
Mother, are you okay?
Your color faded!
Zehra, run!
Bring water! Mother!
I am fine, daughter.
This is how it is to be old.
I can't catch my breath time to time.
Zehra, take Holofira to the tent.
Let her sleep and rest.
I will, mother.
You are not well.
We should see a healer.
Ayse.
I know my time is coming.
Mother, what are you talking about?!
- I'll see Kumral Abdal.
- Sit down, daugter.
Sit down.
I did what I could do.
The rest is Allah's command.
My wish is to live long enough to see
Osman and my sons return.
We waited for
this victory too long, daughter.
Mother, my beautiful daughter.
Don't talk like that, please.
Dying before Osman returns with victory
is not appropriate for me.
Listen to me very well now.
If I can't make it...
There are packs in the chest.
Give them to my grandchildren.
Mother.
Hay Masha Allah Hatuns.
Hay Masha Allah (praise be)
They want to burn us in this caslte.
Let's ruin their game!
But...
I don't like fighting with
the infidel's sword at all.
It's a relic.
I go down but my swords don't.
They need to cut my arms to
take these swords from me.
A sword lives longer than Adam, Cerkutay.
Bamsi Bey's swords witnessed many wars.
Masha Allah, you take care of his relics
very well.
I do, right?
You glorify it.
Bilecik soldiers will hand us the castle
without fighting...
...when they see how eager you are
for the war.
- I was a good warrior, Gunduz Bey.
- I know, Cerkutay.
But I learned the process of war
from you.
The right way is tough.
There is shahada.
I thought Cerkutay wouldn't die.
A sword lives longer than Adam, Gunduz Bey.
I will hand these relics on my son Kayi.
You become soil, I become soil,
Conquerers die...
...but the conquests will remain
as a legacy for generations.
Our dawah is
longer than our lives, Cerkutay. Let's go.
The more infidels we kill the better
until we die.
Our fight shall be blessed!
Let's go.
Let's go sisters.
Trap!
This was your last betrayal.
You shouldn't have done this, Osman!
Where will you run in your own castle?
Allah is eternal!
- Let's go.
Let's go, sisters!
Infidels!
You won't make it!
My Allah, don't let the cruels!
My Creator!
Help my father.
Make infidels fall in their own trap,
my Creator.
- Amin.
One, two, three!
Cerkutay!
My heart is on the right.
Malhun!
Bala!
Are you okay?
You will never get your children, Osman!
Never!
Where are you going?
Don't let anyone pass.
Be careful.
Where are you running, Justinianus?
I'll shed your dirty blood.
Soldiers, attack!
Come to me, dog herd!
Come on.
Come on, today is shahada day!
Hatuns!
The dungeon is on this way.
This way! Hurry up!
Cerkutay, delay them with Hatuns.
Come on Hatuns!
You'll drop away one by one
until we end you all.
Your owner's end will be worse.
Come on Hatuns!
Let's go Bala!
Kids!
My valiants!
Hold on my valiants!
Ignoble Justinianus.
What if they did something bad, Osman?
No.
His life is dependant on my sons' lives.
He'll use them to
get out of the castle.
My Bey.
They must have used the secret passage.
- This way.
- We leave at once!
The secret passage is on this way.
Come on hurry up!
Get them!
My Bey, we'll take care of them.
You go.
Go save the kids, Osman.
Come on Osman Bey.
Go.
Come on!
My father will make you pay for this, Lord.
Prepare your grave.
The only thing your father will do
is to die with his sons!
I'll hang your corpse in the square!
Move!
My Bey!
I know where to go.
Show up on their way, my Bey.
Eyvallah Temur.
Eyvallah.
You are running to your death, Justinianus.
Your time is up.
Come on, to the horses!
It's impossible to take this castle.
Let's save our lives to seek revenge!
You vile heathen!
You are the traitor!
Your life nor your castle...
you will be saving neither.
Don't come closer, Osman.
They'll both die!
You attempted to kill my wives
and children.
Don't, Osman.
We can come to an agreement.
Where the words end...
the weapon of justice speaks!
Don't, Osman!
Don't!
The end of all the tyrants will
be like you.
Either by my hands...
or by another valiant man who holds the
weapon of justice!
My children!
Father!
My lion!
Are you alright?
I am, father.
Mashallah.
-What about you, Alahaddin?
-We are alright, father
My lions!
My lions.
Your uncle's son, Aktemur.
Your brother.
My shehzads!
Mashallah.
Lions!
My lions!
Osman Bey is coming!
Long live Osman Bey!
My children.
You.
Go to everyone Basilleus knows.
And say that I ask for ransom
for the soldiers. Two chests of gold.
Come on.
Orhan! My valiants!
Mother!
My child!
My son!
Thank Allah!
Are you alright?
I'm alright, mother.
Orhan! My Orhan!
Are you alright?
You are fine, right?
Thank you, my bey.
Mashallah.
Take them all to the dungeon.
Come on.
Thank Allah, my bey.
Thank Allah.
Kızılbeyoğlu Tribe
May I enter, Barkın Bey.
Come in.
Speak, beys.
What brings you here.
We are against you taking Söğüt.
If you attempt this...
our alps won't restrain from
killing you.
I told you why I'm doing it.
But you didn't understand it.
Then, I was lying.
Now, I'll speak the truth.
Osman will die!
I'll have Söğüt!
It'll be mine!
May I enter, my bey?
Come in.
My bey, he is waiting for you.
Bury them without getting seen.
Salam Alaikum.
Allah Almighty speaks the truth.
Alaikum Salam, Akça.
Come.
It's for the sahur time, my sheik.
It's apparent that you didn't just come
to bring me my sahur meal, Akça.
Speak what your heart has.
Thank Allah.
Bilecik Castle is a battlefield
since this evening, my sheik.
Do we have information?
Our brothers sent the news, my sheik.
Osman Bey triumphed in Bilecik Castle.
Thank Allah for this victory.
Take care of our visitor Kosses.
Provide everything he needs.
And...
our guest also get the benefit
from Qur-an.
If he wishes, someone should
read him Qur-an.
As you say, my sheik.
Thank you.
That will never do!
One who can't control his anger
is destined to lose, Nikola.
Being powerful is directing your anger
at your enemies.
Not at yourself.
This was the last.
Be patient, Nikola.
Be patient.
Should I be patient, Master Darius?
What else did I do all this time?
I'm being patient.
Isn't it time to get the fruit?
Destroying the ammunition Osman
gathered to conquer İnegöl...
will be a beautiful fruit
from your patience, Nikola.
I don't want to wait for
a moment.
I won't sleep before hurting Osman.
Then, you won't stay sleepless
for long.
Because, our first job will be
destroying that headquarters.
You summoned me, master.
What did Osman Bey do?
He made Bilecik home for the Turks!
-What did Osman Bey do?
-Killed the tyrant!
What did Osman Bey do?
He saved the oppressed!
He opened the door for many
conquests!
Allahu Akbar!
On this sacred Ramadan night, we are
grateful to Allah for this destiny!
Bilecik Castle...
belongs to the Turks now!
Allahu Akbar!
We'll have our sahur meal
here, right?
We will.
We'll eat our sahur and iftar meals in
many places together.
Inshallah.
Bilecik Castle...
will belong to the Turks and Islam
forever!
The flag of the Turks will wave!
The sounds of our azans will
not be silenced!
Our iftars and sahurs will be done
in these lands.
Brothers!
Valiants!
This is a difficult road.
But you weren't afraid.
Thank you.
You always stood with us.
And you made the conquest
easier.
Hatuns.
You always stood behind me.
Thank you.
We did.
We don't want to anymore.
We want to run after conquests now.
We won't stand.
We'll dream for more, as long
as we breath.
Inshallah, my bey.
We'll raise our children
with that dream.
Inshallah.
Our target is İnegöl.
This Friday, we'll be together
next to İnegöl walls.
And inshallah, we'll do our iftar
in İnegöl.
It's time for conquest now!
Bilecik Castle belongs to the Turks!
But never forget!
We are only holding them for now.
Everything belongs to Allah only.
We fight and conquest for Allah.
Until there is no place without
Allah's name...
Allahu Akbar!
Sheik Edebalı...
while you are fasting...
I won't feel good about having this soup.
You'll drink, Kosses.
It's to heal you.
Know that, Islam cares about human life
more than anything else.
You need to have this soup for
your health.
Once you have it, we'll acquire merit.
You'll be helping us.
If you say so...
Thank you, Selcan Hatun.
May it heal you.
Osman loves that soup.
Now I know the secret behind
Osman's victories.
Not at all.
I wanted to see them...
return safe and sound.
My Allah who made the
conquest of Bilecik easy...
will make their return to
the tribe easy too.
With Allah's approval,
you'll see them.
Be at ease.
Inshallah.
Inshallah, my sheik.
Osman Bey is coming.
Thank Allah, he is here.
My valiants are here.
With the name of Allah.
Osman Bey is coming!
My Allah destined him with conquest.
We are grateful forever...
for protecting our children.
Thank you!
Welcome, my bey!
O' people!
Bilecik Castle now belongs to the Kayı!
Allahu Akbar!
Osman...
Mother?
Allahu Akbar!
Mother!
Mother Selcan!
Mother! Mother!
Mother!
Mother, are you alright?
Bring some water!
Mother!
Drink it.
Drink it. Drink it.
It's time to hand over the trust, son.
Mother...
Orhan...
Alahaddin...
Where are they?
My children...
Always protect each other.
Follow the path of your
ancestors.
Watch out for each other.
I promise, grandmother.
Kayı's brave women.
I'm leaving you behind...
so, I'm not concerned.
You'll expand the state...
as you raise your children.
You'll always make things easier
for Osman.
Give me your blessing, mother.
It's yours, my pretty girl.
Mother.
Yes.
I made many mistakes.
I broke your heart.
Did you forgive me?
Gündüz.
I know your heart.
You never break any heart
knowingly.
You have my blessing.
Always watch your brother's back.
Osman.
Mother.
Son.
Be at ease.
My time is over.
Gündoğdu.
Gündoğdu is waiting for me.
And a great state awaits you
with many victories.
May Allah keep you on the right
way.
Don't be sad.
Don't be sad, son.
On the eternal path, we'll
meet again, inshallah.
I bear witness that there is no god
but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad is
the servant and Messenger of Allah.
Mother.
You were like this as a boy too.
You would go, be alone when
you have trouble.
You would understand it and
come to me.
You would cure my pain
as a motherless child.
How can I repay you, mother.
What payment between a mother
and a child, son?
I cured your longing
for a mother...
and you cured my longing
for a child.
Mother.
Now, it'll be more difficult for you.
It's time to repair what you've
broken.
I separated you from
your child.
Give me your blessing, my girl.
It's yours, mother.
Thank Allah! Thank Allah!
Will you take good care
of my daughter?
I will, mother.
I give my permission!
-My pretty girl.
-So glad I have you, mother.
So glad we have you.
Always, my girl.
Go to your mother.
My son!
Mother.
''Verily we belong to Allah and verily to
Him do we return.''
End of the episode 91
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com